This love in my heart,
it will burn on forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
No matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting bones,
we'll reach it, we are home.
I'm
so truly grateful.
I ran into you on that day so long ago.
We laughed every moment
with tears in our eyes.
Till we knew we weren't alone.
The blowing wind came in
and joined us on our way.
And with it I know we'll rise.
We'll be flying up high.
Why, tell me why are you giving up?
Why, tell me why you want to fight alone?
Hey, what kind of future
do you think you have?
Your dream is already in your hands.
This love in my heart,
it will burn off forever!
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
I don't matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting possible
reaching, we are home.
From the horizon, out on
the edge of the world.
If there is a place that I want to
take you to, let's head for it then!
But as for the way, we already know.
We promised it long ago.
You scream by your voice.
That can't break through the silence.
Feeling defeated.
It crushes your helpless heart.
I've got your back, I swear.
I'll always be here.
Let's put our fate within
this light under the sun.
Can you close your eyes and
just listen to my voice?
Let's find the answer together I'm
telling you in our path I trust that it
will lead us To another sea untarded
Cause now we are home On the horizon,
out on the edge of the world
There is a place that I want
to take you to Let's head for
it then But after the way,
we already know
We promised it long ago
One problem
Big Mom's death doesn't mean anything
to me either way But I question
if she's even the kind of person who
can be killed with guns or cannons
From my impression of her,
she's like a giant metal blimp How
do you take someone like that down?
Valid point.
We only get one shot at this
assassination, and it has to be good.
Who knows what will happen
if we're unsuccessful.
So emperors, huh?
They're that tough?
Of course.
She's a monster.
I kid you not, our lives were at stake
when we tried to get Brooke back.
And she was asleep.
Don't underestimate her.
This woman previously murdered
her own son for some sweets.
I'm curious as to why you chose
the tea party to attempt this?
Won't all of her officers
be in attendance?
It seems risky.
I figured you'd ask something like that!
I'm gonna put this bluntly.
Under just the right circumstances,
I can offer in five seconds.
That's fashionable!
You heard correctly, Lili.
However, creating that window of time
will prove to be a bit difficult, you see.
Her pirate crew is not only
formidable, but quite substantial, too.
We will lose complete
control of the situation
if we are noticed by one of her people,
Lili.
If that happens, we're
looking at an Alto war.
Ninety-night us.
The plan is already in motion.
It all began with the
capture of Caesar here.
It's Gastino and don't you dare call me
that name in front of Big Mom either.
Now listen you better make
good on your promise and give
me back my heart once we
accomplish our goal that's the
agreement right don't forget
and if you're screwing with
me I won't hesitate to take the
life of your first born son.
My veggies a man of his word.
Guess he co Don't worry
he always comes through.
Not he go.
Who cares what we call him.
He's nothing but human garbage.
Either way.
Anyway.
What's his name?
Still has an important role.
Naturally I can't wait to
show you what I've been up to.
Deadly poison gas kx launchers.
One's plenty but I made
extras because why not?
There's five whole grams
of organophosphate.
in every deadly shot one
shot and it's r .i .p
rotten poison it's the
most diabolical weapon
In all existence and it's made by moi mere
skin contact can kill
almost any average person
just imagine when you
inject it in the body
i'm a hundred no two hundred
percent sure you'll die
you'll die oh sweet glorious death
we get the point enough already so
you're saying that one shot from this
weapon should do the job sadly it
ain't that simple even if we nail
her with it it won't do a damn if
she's in perfect health the shot alone
will be able to break that woman's
thick skin.
Frankly, you won't find many weapons
that will work against that broad.
So, what was the point of
creating those launchers?
You didn't let me finish yet.
I said it would be
a waste to try when the thing was healthy.
In order for these to get the job
done, we need to meet Some conditions.
Two of them, for starters,
we need to make sure that no
one can stop us for at least.
Five seconds.
Secondly, Mama's gonna need to
be in a weakened state somehow.
Oh, is that all?
What a walk in the park.
As it so happens,
everything's gonna line up
real nice at the tea party.
Don't cry, Pez.
Aw, Daddy's sorry.
He can get wildy sometimes.
Don't cry, baby.
It's been a little over a year since
we first allied with Mumsy Woomsies.
I think you forgot to drop the baby talk.
Yet we've never seen it take a lick.
We watched her wreck a whole city.
She's been riddled with bullets
and pelted by cannonballs.
That bird even sank a ship.
She always walks away without
a single bruise on her body.
You really pegged her when you
compared her to a metal blimp before.
However,
I know for a fact that
bug-eyed Betty can still
get banged up Because I saw
it with my own two peepers
The incident with Mother
Carmel's photo, hello
Very good, Vito
At every tea party,
there's this one picture that
is placed at the table setting
directly across from Mama No
one is allowed to sit there
She treats this item like
it's some kind of treasure.
A picture?
That's right.
It's a frame with Mother
Carmel's portrait inside it.
Dead object is Mama's only known weakness.
So who is that person, then?
We don't know the details, but
Mama seems indebted to her.
She's a mystery, otherwise.
So you think she's dead?
We heard she disappeared.
Mama's missing. Mother?
How peculiar.
Nobody knows anything.
Not even the family.
At this Once party,
a servant accidentally knocked the
mother carmel frame off the table.
I was completely stunned
by Mama's reaction to it.
Her face went pale.
And she let out a tremendous
shriek like I'd never heard before.
It was a much different fit
than her normal hunger pains.
All we could do was cover our ears to
protect ourselves until it was over.
It was so shrill, it even caused
some attendees to pass out.
In addition to the scream,
she unleashed her own conqueror's
Haki upon the party-goers that day.
All because someone dropped the picture.
Now we're just getting to the good part.
You're not gonna believe this but
when Mama fell down to her knees
I saw that she scraped them enough
to bleed they stopped dead in my
tracks because I thought this
monster didn't bleed red like a human
when she breaks down like that her
body loses its defensive properties
so at the tea party
today what do you suppose
will happen when we
smash that picture that
pieces.
Mama will be in utter shock and we'll get
at least five seconds where everyone will
be paralyzed from the cry.
Then it's the KX Launcher's time to shine.
And the world will have One less emperor.
The news about the assassination of Big
Mom will spread through the whole world.
What about the screen, though?
Won't we be paralyzed as well?
Not to worry.
We'll have these.
The invisible Symphonia system.
Perfect.
Earplugs, huh?
If just breaking a picture's
gonna create such a huge mess,
then let's use that time to
save Sanji's family, too.
Listen.
This ain't gonna be that easy.
We will have approximately three seconds
before Mama's fit into picture-breaking.
The man in the thick
of it'll be surrounded
by angry big mom pirates
before all the chaos.
Surviving that alone will be no cakewalk.
And that's the part where
you'll come in, Straw Hat.
You up for it?
Hang on just a minute.
You're just going to
use Luffy to bait them?
Listen, Veggie.
Numbi and her friends saved Lola's life.
You can't use them like
some kind of sacrifice.
Okay.
Yeah, sounds fun. What?
Hold on, can we vote at least?
Perhaps we should reevaluate
things before we commit.
Nah, I got an idea.
When I show up, it's gonna
blow everybody's mind.
You'll see.
Huh?
Please elaborate, I'm lost here.
Whoa, are you gonna do a
magic trick or something?
Tell me what it is!
Yeah, yeah!
No way, that'll spoil the surprise. What?
Well, he seems confident.
It's a deal, then.
You better pull this off, boyo. Uh-huh.
Now, so it clear you know when you're
supposed to break the picture, right?
Yeah, of course.
It's when Sanji kisses pudding.
I'm not kissing her. Won't happen.
Everyone at the whole
wedding will turn their eyes.
To the kiss.
Once her veil is lifted,
literally and figuratively,
Pudding will attempt to shoot Sanji.
I'll dodge the bullet, no kiss.
So you can let the
gunshot be your cue. Easy.
That works for me.
All right.
Let's go over the plan
once more just to be sure.
First, Pudding shoots the gun.
And while everyone's distracted,
Straw Hat breaks the picture.
Big Mom lets out a big scream.
But that don't bother us.
We pull out the invisible symphonia
system and stick them in our ears.
They're just earplugs.
Then it's like taking candy from a baby.
While the guests are in a panic, you
swoop in and save those Jermagoons.
Then we grab the KX launcher,
loaded with a poison shot.
Then send big mom to her maker we
wrap everything up in 10 seconds!
Stops capiche?
As soon as we know that big mom's out,
this boob is gonna enter the scene.
Even to this boo, what did you call me?
Hate that guy! Yeah?
Why do we have to work with him?
You're so rude!
Use your brain!
Since I can fly,
I'll dive onto the scene with a mirror to
create an easy escape route for everyone.
Characterity of her ability
mama's gonna kill me for this.
Don't force me to help you
Capturing Barrel here
was a stroke of genius.
You did a bang-up job if
we're trying to escape
ain't nobody's power gonna
be more useful than hers
Soon as you finish your dirty work,
dive right into Caesar's mirror.
Big Mom's still gonna be
shrieking her head off?
So you should have just enough time.
Once we're in the mirror
dimension, we can run away safely.
There's no quicker and no safer way to
get off the island, I guarantee that much.
We'll be back on the sunny and taking off
before they even realize what hit them.
Quite the sophisticated plan we've got.
Yep, it'll be easy.
Sneaky bastards.
Once each of us gets to our own
ships, the alliance is kaput.
Haul ass out of enemy
territory and don't look back.
Good luck out there.
You too.
It seems that everything is settled.
The tea party doesn't kick
off until 10 o 'clock, right?
We've got two and a half hours.
I'd better head back to my room for now.
They'll be looking for me.
We gotta move, too.
Somebody's gotta pretend
to be security, you know.
They know.
Hey, Veggie, could you do me a favor?
What is it?
Okay, so when I make my big
funny entrance, could you...
Wait, funny?
No.
Why are you trying to be funny?
The day of the tea party, it's a holiday!
Bring out the beer and supreme cheese!
Time to party!
But foul lady put it in a groom already?
Yeah, and he's the prince from
the Kingdom of Germany, no less.
We'll have a strong new ally!
The entire Dufeld conglomerate
is here for the wedding.
It shall be a star-studded affair,
I can assure you that much.
To the bride!
A little too early for that, buddy!
It's fine, we got more confetti.
Master Sanji's wedding.
Can you believe it?
They said we can't go
inside the castle today.
Kind of a shame.
I was hoping we could escort
our prince to the big event.
Well, we are soldiers.
They probably don't want us at a wedding.
I guess it should be a day of peace, huh?
Hello and good morning to
everyone in the Vinsmoke family.
Yonji, wake up and change!
Anyone seen Reiju?
She's not in her room
Now that you mention it,
I don't think I've seen her
since yesterday afternoon.
Oh, there's no need to worry!
Lady Reiju is making
preparations in another room.
I see.
I merely wanted to check in.
There's still an hour
before the tea party?
take your time.
What happened, Mama? Are you okay?
Call the ministers now!
It's not moving.
It's dead.
My lovely little skeleton man is broken.
Hey, let's look on the bright side, okay?
Yeah, you've got the big tea party today
that you've been looking forward to.
And you know what that means, don't you?
The wedding cake!
Mama, I'm pleased to report that Mr.
Morgans and the other VIPs have
already arrived on the island.
You are not going to get away with this.
You untie me this instant. Get out.
We'll leave some food
and water, all right?
And don't worry.
I'm sure someone will come for you.
You kidding me?
And what's this all about?
Where are you going? Get out.
We're leaving this land. What?
So you packed all your
stuff last night and now
you're trying to sneak off
without so much as a word?
I'm sorry.
Your crew's an affiliate
of the Big Mom Pirates.
That means you're not
allowed to leave the country.
This is an open act of
betrayal against Mama.
Did you even have the guts to face her?
What good would that do us?
Try to leave here and you die.
That's how she operates, right?
Jinbei expresses his gratitude to you.
And what does that mean?
We were very fortunate to
hear the truth from Peckums.
Veggie's plan to assassinate Big
Mom seems a bit far-fetched to me,
but I suppose it's no less
surprising than Mama's
plan to assassinate all of
the Vinsmoke family at once.
At any rate, if Luffy finds out about this,
he'll brave any danger to rescue Sanji.
The lives of his entire
crew will be at risk.
I cannot simply sit back
and watch them perish
therefore I'm left with no
other choice I must raise
a rebellion I will betray
big mom openly I felt
the sense of duty to her
so I tried telling her
directly that I wanted
to leave but that plan
was a failure thanks to
the sacrifice required by
her roulette the The
numbers written upon that
cruel device represented
the lives of my comrades.
That's why I need all of
you to flee from this place.
The price that Big Mom required of
me was an unreasonable sanction,
extended far past the
value of my own life.
On the day of the tea
party, security will be lax.
The hors d 'oeuvre ships will be
busy escorting the guests instead.
And attention will be
even further diverted
if something shocking
happens at the tea party!
It will be the perfect chance to escape
even with a firm plan
this will be dangerous.
I'm prepared for that we
support you there's nothing
in this world we want more
than for you to be free!
Thank you and I know that you
don't get it joining Straw Hat
is one thing but you're Too eager
to sacrifice yourself for him.
It's quite simple.
Luffy is my friend, but I would be
proud to call him captain as well.
Huh?
As a pirate,
it is my duty and it would be my honor
to offer my life to a worthy captain.
As for when, that doesn't matter.
I've already made up my mind.
I see.
Well, I won't try to stop you.
But while you're saving Straw Hat's life,
do your best to save
your own life as well.
Understand?
Everyone prepare to set
sail for Fishman Island.
The Ryugu Kingdom is worth
fighting for, right? Of course.
Then we'll protect it,
no matter what it takes.
I am grateful.
It's nothing.
We've been friends for decades now.
We'll live to see each other again.
I'm certain.
What you mean?
Jim Bay expresses his gratitude to me.
Did he say something to mama
that I don't know about?
Is everyone ready to leave?
Hey, you.
Where the hell have you been?
That's none of your business.
I changed my room because you were.
and I didn't want to sit
through that nonsense.
Hear that, Yonji?
She's too fancy for us.
No fighting.
Once we reach the rooftop,
sit still for the tea party.
It's a proud day.
Germa Double Six will soon
regain its former influence.
With Big Mom's power at our side,
we shall conquer the North Blue,
just as we did in the past.
Good times for you, then.
Assuming Sanji doesn't screw it all up.
Hey, buddy, the groom
didn't run away, did he?
He and the bride are fully prepared.
I assure you
What are you thinking Sanji?
Why didn't you escape like I told you to
know what's going to happen if you stay?
So depressing getting cold
feet jitters on your big day.
Does that sound like pudding to you?
It's all so annoying.
What if that dumbass Sanji
bleeds on me after I kill him?
Oh, yeah?
And if I want everyone to
believe I'm a good girl again,
I'll have to erase all
their memories one by one.
Yeah, yeah.
Can you even imagine that?
It's going to be a major pain in the ass.
The players are gathered.
Their objectives are clear.
Now, at last, the blood-stained
tea party shall begin.
Everybody go, it's time to go!
Don't you know?
Time for the show!
Watch out now!
Here's Spokeswagon rushing to the throne!
Will he make it there in time?
Before the clock strikes!
So just a little more!
Rockets are here!
Look at the rocket!
We can't wait to see!
So, let's go.
I don't know.
Dock, what a joke.
This is a wedding.
Who invited him?
We're so hypocritical.
You don't get to judge.
He can see them to a
chapel as easy as a grave.
Hey now, wait a sec.
I can smell the stench of blood on you.
So shut up.
Don't test me.
My, what a lovely day.
I'm grateful I was asked to call.
It's morning.
This marriage is gonna be big news.
And my company has ties to Jen?
So what?
The underworld already knows.
Who cares about old news?
No one who will care.
No one wants a ship old news!
So get with it.
Hi, hello?
How are you?
What a pleasure.
Leaders of the underworld.
Please hurry.
If you continue through the gate,
you'll sadly be so liggity late.
But luckily I have a shortcut
that can take you to the club.
A candy escalator.
This artwork is a sight to see.
So great, this candy scopes is a simple.
Very artistic.
I am humbled by your words.
But Mama hates late arrivals, you know.
So, let's be on our way.
Ooh, the staircase is moving.
Rather elegant, isn't it?
Convenient?
I'll give it that Have a safe trip.
Here, for you.
If you can wait for three minutes,
then you'll be free to lick
the candy escalator as well.
Now, time to lickety-split.
It smells lovely.
Welcome everyone.
This place always with your appetizer.
Glad to see you all! Could make it.
Hello, smoothie.
Might I offer you a drink today?
We have a piece of Mount Maori lava.
A beautiful woman who stabbed
a thousand men and a giraffe.
That sounds really funny when it screams.
I'll have a cup of the giraffe.
Same for me. All right.
Let me squeeze it.
Here, enjoy.
Oh, tastes great, and
it's smooth going down.
Come on, open up!
Screw your body, search,
let me out! Sorry, Mr.
Jigra, no can do.
Let me go!
Let me go, you damn punks!
Is big mom already inside you know i got
an invitation for the last tea party too?
But for the life of me i couldn't go
i had to go to my mother's funeral!
So i would let her as an apology i'm
just one guest why should big mom care?
Then do you know what she did?
She sent me a box with
my poor sick fat as...
Hey, that man is a guest here.
Who shot him?
Huh?
It was you?
Street General, Katakuri! Could he?
Why'd you kill him?
This is what he was gonna say.
I'm just one guest.
Why should Big Mom care?
Do you know what she did?
She sent me a box with my
poor sick father's head in it.
I'm here today to finally get my revenge.
Now open the gate.
Bang.
He fires his gun again.
Two of your men go down,
taken completely by surprise.
So I threw a jelly bean at him to stop
that undesirable outcome from happening.
Is that a problem?
Rook, Buggy?
Tell Mama that it was my call.
I know what you're gonna say next.
I see.
All right, then.
This Bruno, he is going to be
a pain in the ass at the party.
He trained his observation Haki so
much he can see into the future,
for a couple of seconds at least.
The bastard's bounty is over a billion.
He's a monster.
I see.
All right, then.
Seems like the time's arrived.
Finally, the tea party is here.
Why hello there?
Thank you for coming out!
Sweet as far as the eye can see!
So raise those glasses
and everybody be happy?
Come on, eat!
And drink!
Have the time of your life!
Because this is a very special day.
We've got some wonderful surprises.
I'm sure they'll knock you off your feet.
Thank you.